<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<song id="6">
	<title>The Tired Influencer</title>
	<artists>
		<artist id="2">Gorillaz</artist>
	</artists>
	<genres>
		<genre id="2" />
	</genres>
	<duration seconds="210" /> 
	<lyrics lang="en" format="txt">
	[Verse 1: 2D & Siri]
(One second)
It's a cracked screen world
Where white blooms above the city (I'm sorry)
Catch sunrise and the freeway glows
Perfumed with palo santo (Here's what I found)
Early flights touch down (I didn't get that, could you try again)
(Here's what I found)

[Chorus: 2D & Siri]
Every day, the Tired Influencer (I didn't get that, could you try again)
You're sleeping deep, waiting for an answer (Here's what I found)
Gotta press on brown eyes
I always keep you close beside me
Million dreams (Here's what I found)
'Cause that's the way it's meant to be
(I found this on the wеb)
(If your love)

[Verse 2: 2D & Siri]
It was a different timе (Different time)
I hear that a lot up in the hills (In the hills)
Logic kills and Silver Lake reflections (Reflections)
(I don't have the answer for that, is there something else I can help you with?)
Just trying to keep my head up (My head up)
Nothing real anymore
See Gorillaz Live
Get tickets as low as $197

You might also like
Tarantula
Gorillaz
Silent Running
Gorillaz
Feel Good Inc.
Gorillaz

[Chorus: 2D & Siri]
In the world of The Tired Influencer (I didn't get that, could you try again)
You're sleeping deep, waiting for an answer (Here's what I found)
Gotta press on brown eyes
I always keep you close beside me
Million dreams (Here's what I found)
'Cause that's the way it's meant to be

[Outro: 2D & Siri]
If you're lost (Please try again)
Is it meant to be? (I don't have the answer for that, is there something else I can help you with?)
If your love (I'm not sure I understand)
Wear your love, wear your love, wear your love (Interesting question)
Is it meant to be? (Wear your love, wear your love, wear your love)
Is meant to be (Wear your love, wear your love, wear your love)
(I found this on the web)
(I don't have the answer for that)
	</lyrics>
	<album id="6" />
</song>